Guide to the School of Art and Architecture, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the dean, 1945-1968; Accession 1996-A-018
  - Phillips, John Marshall, Article in Associates' Bulletin, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Phillips, John Marshall, Correspondence Regarding Death, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Phillips, John Marshall, Correspondence with Harvard Press, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Phillips, John Marshall, Acknowledgments for Contributions, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Phillips, John Marshall, General Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Photograph and Slide Collection, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Photographic Society of America, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - President's Office, 1947-1961 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Projects Committee, 1947-1950 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Provost's Office, 1947-1960 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - P -Miscellaneous, 1947-1961 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Rabinowitz File, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Registration Lists, 1947-1954 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Registration Lists, 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Registration Lists, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - R -Miscellaneous, 1947-1961 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Safety Council, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Sawyer, C.H. Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Sculpture Department, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Secondary School Student Prospects, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Secretary's Office, 1947-1959 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Service Bureaus, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Slide and Photograph Collection(Art Library), 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Societe Anonyme, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Statistics, Etc., 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - S -Miscellaneous, 1947-1961 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - T -Miscellaneous, 1947-1961 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - UCLA Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - University Council, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - University Council, Architecture, Painting, and Sculpture Sub-Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - University Council, Architecture, Painting, and Sculpture Sub-Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - University Council, Committee on Art and Architecture, 1955-1961 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - University Council, Drama Sub-Committee, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - University Development Office, 1958-1959, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - University Health Department, 1957-1959,1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - U -Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Veterans Office, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - V -Miscellaneous, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - W -Miscellaneous, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - W -Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Yale Arts Association, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Yale College, 1951-1956 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Yale College, Freshman Year, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Yale Club, Exhibition Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Yale Development Committee, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Yale Farms, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - XYZ -Miscellaneous, 1947-1950 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - XYZ -Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Budget and Salaries, 1946-1968 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - Budget and Salaries, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - City Planning, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Job Recommendations, 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Job Requests From Other Institutions, 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Teacher Placement Office, 1956-1960 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Yale College, 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 147)
- Scrapbook and records relating to Wilma Wolf, 1947; Accession 1996-A-027
  - Scrapbook, 1958-1969, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Records relating to Wilma Wolf, 1947 (Box 2)
- School of Art & Architecture committee meetings, procedures, memos, and records, 1969-1971; Accession 1997-A-017
  - Minutes, procedures, & memos
  - 1969 Sep -1970 May (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1970 Aug -1971 Jul (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Records of the dean, circa 1961-1970; Accession 2001-A-010
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
  - A and A Catalogue, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Material to Be Saved, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Architecture, Dept. of, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Correspondence (Yale Arts Association), 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Day, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Fund, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Applicants for Positions, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Art, Dept. of, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - b-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Survey in Yale in Fine Arts, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Building and Grounds Committee, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - C-Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Art and Architecture Centennial, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chairman's Annual Reports 61-68, 1961-1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - College Work Study Program, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - City Planning, Dept. of, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Campus Police, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - A and A Catalogue, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Coffee House, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Computer Conf. (H.S.W.), Grant and Correspondence Relative to, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Computer Graphics Seminar, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - E-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Eye Magazine Correspondence, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Eye Correspondence, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Faculty and staff lists and notices, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Fellowships and scholarship, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Film Making, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - f-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Film Catalogues, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Graphic Design Program, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Graduate Record Exam, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - G-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - I-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - H-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - JobOpportunities and Recommendations, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - J. Miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Veterans Administration, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Candidates for Degree, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Teaching List of Graduates, 1928-1972 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Thesis Information, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - b. Chaet -- Correspondence, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Alumni Exhibition -12 Yale Artists, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Benefit Print Show, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Exhibitions, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Exhibitions Students and Faculty, 1961-1970 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Secretary's Office, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Summer, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Space Allocation, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Summer 1968 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - T-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Undergraduate Programs, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - University: General Information Announcements, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - University Council, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - University Directory, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - U. Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - V-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - W.miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Weaver, Howard S. - Personal, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Yale Corporation, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - X-y-z Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Art Council of Greater New Haven, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Art Council, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Arts Council of Greater New Haven, Inc, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Business Aircraft Accident, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Business Aircraft Accident, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Business Aircraft Contributors, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Business Aircraft Operating Costs, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Business Aircraft Service Order, Bill of Sale, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Civil Air Patrol, Connecticut Wing Advisory Council, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Comptroller's Office: Bills sent for payment, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Comptroller's Office: Check Requests, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Yale Reports Correspondence with David Walker, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Yale Reports General Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Yale Reports Television, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Yale Reports Television, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Yale University Press Committee on Printing and Design, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Yale University Press Printing Office, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Yale University Press Printing Office, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - JobSeeker, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Harvard Board of Overseers, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Internal Relations, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - 1945w 25th Reunion, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Alumni Reunion 1945w 25'h Reunion, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Save the Park, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Weaver, Personal Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - House Repairs, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Weaver: Personal Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - K-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Lecture Series, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Library, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - N-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - O-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Provost's Office, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - P-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Perspecta, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Peyre Report Undergrad. Program in Art, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - President's Office, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Q-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - R-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Rentals Available, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Registration, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Student Committee, 1961-1970 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - S-miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Selective Service System, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Graphics Design Program, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - G-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - History of Art, Dept of, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - H-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - I-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - J-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - JobOpportunities and Recommendations, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - K-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Lecture Series, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Library, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - L-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - M-miscelaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - National Council of Fine Arts Deans, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - National Council of the Arts in Education, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - N-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - O-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - President's Office, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - P-miscel laneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Provost's Office, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - R-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Secretary's Office, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Selective Service System, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Student Notices, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Summer Calendars, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Summer Registrations, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - S-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - T-miscelf aneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - U-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - University Council, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - V-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - W-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Yale Club, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - X-y-z Miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Fellowship: Anna Bissell McCay, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - McCay Fellowship-application, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Monroe Traveling Fellowship, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - McCay Scholarship, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Monticello Prize, 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Alumni Board, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Alumni Fund, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Alumni Correspondence (Yale Arts Association), 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Alumni Day, 1967 April 28 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Amer. Council on Education, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - Applications for Positions, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Architecture, Dept. of, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Art, Dept. of, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - A-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Building - Equipment Space Request, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Building Superintendent Building Security, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Building and Grounds Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Buffalo Trip, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - b-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - C-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Center for Environmental Research, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - City Planning - Latin American Program, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - City Planning, Dept of, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Coffee House, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - D-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Dean Danes - speeches, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Faculty and Staff Lists, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - E-miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Campus Police, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - f- Miscellaneous, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 183)
- Faculty minutes, student and financial records, circa 1922-1941; Accession 2001-A-090
  - Inventory, 1932 January (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Instructor's marks, 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Master keys (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class records [grades], 1921-1922 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Class records [grades], 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Class records [grades], 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class records [grades], 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Review [grades], 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - High grades, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Faculty minutes for Dept. of Painting (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Receipt books [check stubs], 1930-1933 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ethel Childe Walker (booklet) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Class photo [missing], 1929
  - Review marks [grades], 1922-1923 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Materials/bills paid, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cage inventory (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Class records [grades], 1921-1922 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Class records [grades], 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Class records [grades], 1918-1919 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Class records [grades], 1917-1918 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Class records [grades], 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Review [grades], 1916 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Review [grades], 1925 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Review [grades], 1923 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Booklet of Yale Courtyards (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Catalog for exhibit curated by Henry Kibel, 1943; Accession 2002-A-038
  - Catalog for exhibit curated by Henry Kibel, 1943 (Box 1)
- Speech by Dean Gibson Danes honoring Professor Luis Ortiz de Zevallos, 1963; Accession 2002-A-074
  - Speech by Dean Gibson Danes honoring Professor Luis Ortiz de Zevallos, 1963 (Box 1)
- Fund raising brochure from the School of Design and Planning titled, "An Opportunity to Participate", circa 1965; Accession 2002-A-084
- Records of the dean of the School of Art and Architecture, 1943-1976; Accession 2002-A-099
  - Development and alumni
    - University Development Office, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Council, 1954-58 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alumni Board, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alumni and Friends, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alumni Fund
      - General
        - 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
    - Committee, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Sample Mailings, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Class Champions, 1959-60, 60-61 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Class Agents, 1959-60 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Comparisons of individual contributions, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Regionalization of Alumni, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Day, 1954 - 1968 (Box 2)
    - General
      - 1954-1958 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - 1959 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
      - 1960 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - 1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
      - 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - 1965 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11-13)
      - 1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Registration Notebook, 1959-61 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Day/Convocation photographs
      - 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - 1964 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - (Alumni Day) Convocation
      - General
        - 1964 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - 1965 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Lectures, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Committee of 40
    - Correspondence, 1961-1962
      - A -H (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - I -P (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Q -Z (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence and lists to be checked, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Lists, miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Faculty
    - Applications for positions, 1961-1966, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 1-5)
    - Job opportunities, 1961-1965, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6-9)
    - Job opportunities and recommendations, 1965-1966, 1968-69 (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
    - Faculty and staff lists, 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 12-15)
    - Faculty notices, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Lecture series, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Art and Architecture mailing lists and lecture series list, 1960-1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Provost
      - 1953, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - 1958-1962 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Senior faculty fellowships and leaves of absence, 1952-1963 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Personnel Within School, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Computer Graphics, 1968-69 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with Barry Bortnick -Harvard (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - "Courses in College", 1968-69 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Carlburg Sculpture (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Medals and awards, architecture and design, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Alumni
    - Yale Arts Association, Alumni & Friends School of Art & Architecture
      - General, 1959-1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Minutes of Meetings, 1958-61 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Class Lists, 1933-63 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Alumni Board
      - General
        - 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Constitution of Alumni Board of Yale University, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Reunion Dinner, Yale AA, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Correspondence
      - General
        - 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        - 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        - 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Alumni Fund
      - Campaign, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Class Agent Letters, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 14-19)
      - Statements, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Alumni newsletter
      - 1962 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - 1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - 1964 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Yale Alumni Organizations, Federation of Alumni Seminars, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Alumni House, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Alumni Magazine, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Robert Frew's Subject Files, 1967-1996
    - Admissions, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 27-31)
    - Own papers and reports, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 32-33)
    - Personal, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence
      - 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - 1970 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - 1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - General, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - University, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Sent, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Received, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Design, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Outside papers and reports, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Outside papers and references, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Past School of Architecture, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - School of Architecture, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous business, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Bibliographies, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Railroad Station Project, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - First year studio, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Athens District High School, #1, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Waterloo, 1967-1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Environmental Design Research Association (EDRA), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - MED Studio, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Conference notices and newsletters, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Robert Frew proposal, 1988-1996 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Computer correspondence, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Computers, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Sabbatical, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Audiotapes
      - Joe Stagg et al., Undated; 1 (Box 24)
  - Dean Charles Sawyer, 1947 - 1956
    - Subject Files Relating to New Art Gallery
      - Program Study, Present Gallery vs New Building, 1951-1953 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Art Gallery Building Fund, 1946-1955 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
      - Budget, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Art Gallery, New Building, correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Art Building Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Art Building Committee, construction, 1952 January-June (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Conferences: minutes, agendas, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence: contracts, specifications, change orders, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Furniture set-up, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - New Building correspondence: telephone, fire escapes, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Electrical, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Heating, plumbing, etc., 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - New Building status report (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Specifications for Mersick plumbing fixtures, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Photo of unknown building (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - New Building curtains, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - New Building miscellaneous correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Harrison, Laurernce S., "Auxiliary Lighting for Museum Galleries", 1950 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Knoll Associates price lists, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Progressive Architecture correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Change Orders, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Kelly, lighting, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Grafton M. Peberdy (G.M.P.) correspondence, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Equipment correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Dedication of New Art Gallery, invitations, replies, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 27)